Guide to the Arthur Levitt, Jr. Papers
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
Arthur Levitt Papers,
1948-2001
Levitt, Arthur, 1931-
26 linear ft. in (53 boxes & 1 oversize box).
Columbia University Rare Book and Manuscript Library, Butler Library, New York, NY 10027
4079912
Biographical Note
Levitt, the 25th Chairman of the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission, was first appointed by President Clinton in July of 1993 and reappointed to a second five-year term in May of 1998. The longest serving Chairman in the history of the Commission, Arthur Levitt retired from the SEC on Feb. 9th 2001.
The SEC is an independant, nonpartisan, quasijudicial regulatory agency with responsibility for administering the federal securities laws. The purpose of these laws is to protect investors in securities markets that operate fairly and to ensure that investors have access to disclosure of all material information concerning publicly traded securities. The Commission also regulates firms engaged in the purchase or sale of securities, people who provide investment advice, and investment companies. Five Commissioners sit on the SEC with one designated as chairman by the President of the United States.
Key successes of Levitt's first term include reforming the debt markets, improving broker sales and pay practices, promoting the use of plain English in investment literature as well as in SEC communications with the public, preserving the independence of the private sector standard setting process, ensuring the independence of accountants, and encouraging foreign companies to list on U.S. markets.
During Chairman Levitt's tenure, the SEC established the Office of Investor Education and Assistance and created the SEC's World Wide Web site, one of the most popular on the internet, which allows the SEC to make all corporate filings available to the public free of charge. Chairman Levitt has been supportive of high-tech and online securities trading. He supported passage of both the Securities Litigation Uniform Standards Act in 1998 and the Private Securities Litigation Reform Act in the 104th Congress. These bills are designed to reduce the number of frivolous class action lawsuits brought primarily against high tech companies in the computer, internet, and biotech industries.
Chairman Levitt has also sought to raise the industry's sales prectice standards and eliminate the conflicts of interest in how brokers are compensated. During his tenure at the SEC, Levitt worked to protect the interests of the individual investor, which manifested itself most clearly in the passage of Regulation FD. Regulation FD, which went into effect in October 2000, mandates that public companies must broadly disseminate material non-public information simultaneously to all investors. In the wake of Regulation FD, webcasting of company conference calls and other investment events has emerged as one of the most efficient and effective ways companies can help immunize themselves against potential selective disclosure issues.
The SEC has worked to sever ties between political campaign contributions and minicipal underwriting business, a practice known as pay-to-play, as well as improving the disclosure and transparency of the municipal bond market. Chairman Levitt tried to introduce rules barring CPA firms from providing consulting services to their audit clients, believing that consulting feed offer an unhealthy temptation to professional services firms that conduct certified audits. Levitt's initiatives were ment with a determined lobbying effort by the accounting industry. Eventually Levitt was forced to water down his proposals and he accepted a requirement that made companies disclose the dollar amount of the audit and consulting fees that they pay.
The Commission, together with the industry, has developed the Profile Prospectus and other plain English guidelines for investment products in an effort to make disclosure documents easier to understand without compromising the value of the information provided to investors.
Before joining the Commission, Mr Levitt owned Roll Call, a newspaper that covers Capitol Hill. From 1989 to 1993, he served as the Chairman of the New York City Economic Development Corporation. And from 1978 to 1989, he was the Chairman of the American Stock Exchange. Prior to joining the American Stock Exchange, Mr Levitt worked on Wall Street for 16 years, serving as a president for Carter Berlind & Weill and Shearson Hayden Stone, Inc. He graduated Phi Beta Kappa from Williams College in 1952 before serving for two years in the Air Force.
Scope and Content
Correspondence, speeches, speech materials, news clippings, subject files, audio and videotapes relating to the professional activity of Arthur Levitt, Jr. The papers and audiovisual material deal primarily with his tenure as the Chairman of the Securities and Exchange Commission (1993-2001), but also contain earlier records, including some materials relating to Levitt's school years at the Polytechnic Preparatory Country Day School and at Williams College, and his work at Hayden Stone, the American Stock Exchange, and the New York Economic Development Corporation, and his advocacy of the National Endowment of the Arts during the 1991-1992 funding controversy. These papers also contain materials relating to his father, Arthur Levitt, Sr., who served for 24 years as New York State Comptroller.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into 2 series:
Series I: Cataloged Correspondence
Series II: Arranged Correspondence
Series III: Speeches and Testimonies
Series IV: Speeches Background Material
Series V: Biographical
Series VI: Printed Materials
Series VII: Arthur Levitt Sr. Papers
Series VIII: Audiovisual Records
Series IX: Digital Materials
Series X: SEC Work Files
Series XI: NEA Controversy
Series XII: Oversized Documents
Series XIII: SEC Correspondents Index
Subjects
United States.--Securities and Exchange Commission.; American Stock Exchange; Hayden, Stone & Co.; National Endowment for the Arts.; New York City Economic Development Corporation.; Polytechnic Preparatory Country Day School.; Williams College.; Levitt, Arthur, 1900-1980.; Securities industry--Laws and legislation; Articles.; Audiotapes.; Certificates.; Memorandums.; Notes.; Photographs.; Reports.; Speeches.; Videotapes.; Civil service.; Stockbrokers.
Access Restrictions
This collection has no restrictions.
This collection is located off-site. You will need to request this material from the Rare Book and Manuscript Library at least twenty-four (24) hours in advance to use the collection in the Rare Book and Manuscript Library reading room.
Acquisition
02/26/2001 M-01-02-26 Papers U.S. Securities & Exchange Commission Gift
Gift of Hilda Harding of the Securities and Exchange Commission, 2001.
- Series I: Cataloged Correspondence
  Original letters to Levitt from US congressmen and US and foreign government members.
  - Bowles, Erskine B. Chief of Staff to the US President to: Arthur Levitt, Jr., Washington, DC, Dec. 18, 1996; Nov. 21, 1997, (1p. t.l.s. with ms. note, 1p. a.c.s.) (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Bush, George H. W. US President to: Arthur Levitt, Jr., Washington, DC; Houston, TX, Sep. 27, 1991; Dec. 14, 1998, (2 t.l.s.) (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Carter, Jimmy US President to: Arthur Levitt, Jr., Washington, DC, Oct. 13, 1978, (1p. t.l.s.) (Box 1, Folder 2A)
  - Clinton, Bill US President to: Arthur Levitt, Jr., Washington, DC, Feb. 1998 - Jan. 2001, (3 t.l.s.) (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Coelho, Tony to: Arthur Levitt, Jr., n.p., Feb. 23, 1995, (1p. a.c.s.) (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Cohen, William US Secretary of Defense to: Arthur Levitt, Jr., Washington, DC, Jul. 14, 1998, (1p. t.l.s.) (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Collins, Susan M. US Senate (R - ME) to: Arthur Levitt, Jr., Washington, DC, Jan. 22, 2001, (1p. a.c.s.) (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Cox, Christopher US House of Representatives (R - CA) to: Arthur Levitt, Jr., Washington, DC, Apr. 10, 1996, (1p. t.l.s.) (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - D'Amato, Alphonse US Senate (R - NY) to: Arthur Levitt, Jr. - Subpoena for Whitewater Investigation, Washington, DC, Oct. 26, 1995, (3p. t.l.s. (faximile)) (Box 1, Folder 8)
    [Subpoena attachment is also signed by Sarbanes, Paul]
  - Daschle, Thomas. U. S. Senate (D - SD) to: Arthur Levitt, Jr., Washington, DC, Mar. 6, 1999, (1p. a.c.s.) (Box 1, Folder 9)
    [Photocopy of Levitt's reply enclosed]
  - Dingell, John D. US House of Representatives (D - MI) to: Arthur Levitt, Jr., Washington, DC, n.d. - Dec. 7, 2000, (4 a.c.s.) (Box 1, Folder 10)
    [News Clippings enclosed]
  - Dinkins, David N. Mayor, New York City to: Arthur Levitt, Jr., New York, NY, Dec. 16, 1993, (1p. t.l.s.) (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Dodd, Christopher J. US Senate (D - CT) to: Arthur Levitt, Jr., Washington, DC, Sep. 8, 1993; Mar. 24, 1999, (2 a.l.s.) (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Donaldson, William H. New York Stock Exchange, Chairman to: Arthur Levitt, Jr., New York, NY, May 26, 1995, (1p. a.l.s.) (Box 1, Folder 13)
    [US SEC Chairman since Jan. 2003]
  - Domenici, Pete V. US Senate (R - NM) to: Arthur Levitt, Jr., Washington, DC, Nov. 28, 1995, (1p. t.l.s. with ms. note) (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Eshoo, Anna G. US House of Representatives (D - CA) to: Arthur Levitt, Jr., Washington, DC, Jul. 1996 - Oct. 1998, (2 a.l.s., 1p. t.l.s., 1 a.c.s.) (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Ewing, Thomas W. US House of Representatives (R - IL) to: Arthur Levitt, Jr., Pontiac, IL, Dec. 22, 2000, (1p. t.l.s.) (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Faircloth, Lauch US Senate (R - NC) to: Arthur Levitt, Jr., Washington, DC, Mar. 15, 1994; Jan. 19, 1995, (2 t.l.s.) (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Fields, Jack US House of Representatives (R - TX) to: Arthur Levitt, Jr., Washington, DC, Jan. 12, 1995, (1p. t.l.s.) (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Ford, Gerald R. US President to: Arthur Levitt, Jr., n.p., Aug. 25, [n.y.], (1p. a.l.s.) (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Ginsburg, Ruth Bader Supreme Court of the US to: Arthur Levitt, Jr., Washington, DC, Oct. 12, 1995, (1p. t.l.s.) (Box 1, Folder 20)
    [enclosed:letter from A. Levitt to: Payne, Hank, President, Williams College, Williamstown, MA]
  - Levitt, Arthur Jr. US SEC to: Payne, Hank, President, Williams College, Williamstown, MA, Washington, DC, Oct. 17, 1995, (1p. t.l.s.) (Box 1, Folder 20)
    [re: Judge Ginsburg Letter of Oct. 12, 1995 - filed under Ginsburg]
  - Gore, Al US Vice President to: Arthur Levitt, Jr., Washington, DC, Jun. 23, 1997, (1p. t.l.s.) (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Hatch, Orrin US Senate (R - UT) to: Arthur Levitt, Jr., Washington, DC, Sep. 11, 1995, (1p. t.l.s.) (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Kennard, William E. Federal Communication Commission (FCC), President to: Arthur Levitt, Jr., Washington, DC, Oct. 29, 2000, (1p. a.c.s.) (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Kerry, John F. US Senate (D - MA) to: Arthur Levitt, Jr., Staten Island, NY, Sep. 19, n.y., (2p a.l.s.) (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Lackritz, Mark E. Securities Industry Association (SIA), president to: Arthur Levitt, Jr., n.p. [Washington, DC], Jan. 1995 - Nov. 1999, (3 a.c.s., 1p. t.l.s. (on cardboard backing), 1 t.d. (faximile)) (Box 1, Folder 25)
    [Typed letter also signed by Zuckenberg, Roy J., SIA Chairman. Enclosed faximile of SIA board of Directors resolution commending Levitt.]
  - Largent, Steve US House of Representatives (R - OK) to: Arthur Levitt, Jr., n.p., n.d., (1p. a.l.s.) (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Murray, Patty US Senate (D - WA) to: Arthur Levitt, Jr., Washington, DC, Mar. 29, 1995, (1p. t.l.s.) (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Panetta, Leon White House Chief of Staff to: Arthur Levitt, Jr., Washington, DC, Oct. 28, 1994, (1p. t.l.s.) (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Rainer, William J. US Commodity Futures Trading Commission to: Arthur Levitt, Jr., Washington, DC, Sep. 10, 1999, (1p. a.l.s.) (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Richardson, William US Secretary of Energy to: Arthur Levitt, Jr., Washington, DC, Dec. 26, 2000, (1p. t.l.s.) (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Reich, Robert Biff, Secretary of Labor to: SEC Chairman (Skip Hayward), Washington, DC, Sep. 10, 1996, (1p. t.l.s., 1p. t.l.s.(copy)) (Box 1, Folder 31)
    [photocopy of Levitt's reply (Sep. 19, 1996) enclosed]
  - Riegle, Donald W., Jr. US Senate (D - MI) to: Arthur Levitt, Jr., Washington, DC, Jan. 21, 1994, (2p. a.l.s.) (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Sheng, Andrew Securities and Futures Commission, Chairman to: Arthur Levitt, Jr., Hong Kong, Sep. 20, 2000, (1p. t.l.s.) (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Stevens, Ted US Senate (R - AK) to: Arthur Levitt, Jr., Washington, DC; AK, Sep. - Dec. 2000, (1p. t.l.s. with ms. note, 1p. t.l. (dictated), 1p. 1, a.c.s. ) (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Udall, Mark E. US House of Representatives (D - CO) to: Arthur Levitt, Jr., Washington, DC, Oct. 25, [2000], (1p. a.l.s., 1p. clipping) (Box 1, Folder 35)
    [Enclosed photocopy of congressional remarks]
  - Levitt, Arthur Jr. Carter. Berlind & Weill, Inc. to: Wilson, Joseph C., Chairman of the Board, Xerox Corporation, New York, NY, Sep. 27, 1966, (2p. t. l.) (Box 1, Folder 36)
    [re: A. Levitt Sr. re-election campaign]
  - Wilson, Joseph C. Xerox Corporation to: Arthur Levitt, Jr., Rochester, NY, Oct. 5, 1966, (1p. t.l.s.) (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Series II: Arranged Correspondence
  - Subseries II.1: Originals
    includes some emails and faximiles. Most correspondence from SEC Correspondence 1993 - 2001scrapbook. Anonimous correspondence filed first.
    - Anderson, Joseph F.; Koppes, Richard - see Aronson, Tracey; [Athis], Paul; Bachman, John W.; Baird, Brent D.; Baker, William; Barr, Clifford; Barry, Grace; Blackmore, Robert L.; Blair, Warren E.; Brodsky, William J.; Brophy, Raymond C.; Brown, David A.; Callaway, Howard H.; Clarkson, James A.; Carey, Paul A.; Catell, Robert B; Cogan, Marshall S.; Critchlow, Paul W.; Damson, Barry; Davidson, Joan; Degenhardt, Harold F.; Derderian, James E.; Dibble, Edward T.; Dilenschneider, Robert L; Dulski, Walter; Edelman, Stanley; Emmott, William; Evans, Carol; Evans, Thomas W.; Fields, Harvey J; Figueres, Muni; Forbes, Malcolm S. (Steve); Fink, Matthew P.; Friedland, Rhoda; Glassman, Mary; Goldin, Harrison J.; Goldsmith, Margie; [Greenbaum], Teddy; Groves, Ray J.; Guggenheim, Charles; Haskell, Janelle; Herman, James A.; [Jores], Michael; Komives, Michael; [Krongard, A. B.] Buzzy Automatic Data Processing - see Weston, Josh S.; Brooklyn Union - see Catell, Robert B; Center for Working Capital - see Tarbox, Monte; Chicago Mercantile Exchange - See Brodsky, William J; Consumer Federation of America - see Metzenbaum, Howard M; Coopers & Lybrand - see McKinney, James E.; Council for Institutional Investors - see Teslik, Sarah; The Economic Club of Chicago - see Barry, Grace; The George Washington University - see Trachtenberg, Stephen Joel; Investment Company Institute - see Fink, Matthew P. General: A - K (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - La Ganga, Charles; Lord, Sandra; Linton, R. E.; Lorne, Simon M; Lufkin, Dan W.; McKane, David B.; McKinney, James E.; McLucas, William R.; Madoff, Bernard L; Madoff, Peter B.; Manley, John M.; Mathisen, Tyler; Metzenbaum, Howard M; Martin, David - see Aronson, Tracey; Minow, Newton N.; Morse, William E.; Nemser, Earl; Nowicki, Elizabeth; Olson, John F.; Payne, Harry C.; Petchesky, Harry J.; Pottruck, David S.; Quinn, Linda C.; Reed, William S.; Rogers, William; Rubinstein, Peter J.; Ruder, William; Scardino, Jennifer; Schadt, James P.; Schlosser, Alfred M.; Schwartz, Robert; Segal, Martin E.; Silverstone, Leslie J.; Smythe, Marianne K.; Sobel, Ronald B.; Sole, Kelly Ann; Sommer, A. A. Jr.; Stanton, Frank; Stone, J. Jacques; Spatz, Theodore; Summers, Laurence; Tarbox, Monte; Teslik, Sarah; Tolleris, Bea; Trachtenberg, Stephen Joel; Walker, Richard H.; Weisbrod, Carl; Wang, [Leo]; Weston, Josh S.; Wilpon, Fred; Woolf, Harry. Los Angeles Times - see Sole, Kelly Ann; Merrill Lynch & Co. - see Critchlow, Paul W.; Ontario Securities Commission - see Brown, David; Poly Prep School - see Petchesky, Harry J.; Salomon Brothers, Inc - see Lorne, Simon; Charles Shwab & Co - see Pottruck, David S.; VEBA; Wellesley College - see Reed, William S.; Williams College - see Payne, Harry C.; General: L - Z (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Andreesen, Matthew; Augustine, Norman A.; Balamaci, Nick; Beard, Sam; Beresford, Dennis R.; Bialkin, Kenneth J.; Bloch, Robert W.; Blaskovich, Fred; Brennan, John J.; Brinkley, James W.; Buffett, Warren E.; Catto, Henry E.; Chin, Faye; Colson, Robert H.; Davies, Howard; Dilenschneider, Robert L.; Emerson, John B.; Fickling, William A., Jr.; Fleischer, Arthur; Goldmark, Peter C., Jr.; Gorman, D. J.; Hopkins, Karen B.; Hunter, David W.; Job, Peter; Kelley, Aloysius P.; Koski-Grafer, Susan; Kraft, Robert K.; Linowitz, Sol M.; Lowenstein, Lou; McDonough, William J.; McIntosh, Bill; McLendon, Heath B.; Malkin, Peter L.; Mikva, Abner J.; Muis, Jules W.; Nemser, Earl; Newman, Fred; Olson, John; Perlman, Jay; Reese, James R.; Ross, Alan; Ross, Richard S.; Schneiderman, Irwin; Schwab, Richard L.; Seligman, Joel; Senatore, Charles V.; Sollazzo, Bob; Steinbrenner, George M, III; Stern, Walter P.; Stevens, Rick; Sturner, William; Sowan, Richard J.; Stalcup, Steve; Till, John G.; Williams, Harold M.; Willmott, Peter S.; Zarr, Gary; Zelinka, Robert. Wall Street Journal Levitt's Resignation from SEC (Box 1, Folder 39)
      [Original correspondence removed from scrapbook of the same name, replaced by photocopies.]
  - Subseries II.2: Congressional photocopies.
    These materials were part of additions, donated by A. Levitt in 2002. Photocopies of SEC chairman correspondence with members of US Senate and US House of Representatives. Fisrt folder contains index for this subseries. Subject files, arranged alphabetically by policy topic. Also includes transcripts of congressional hearings and background materials.
    - Complete Index, 1993 - 2001 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Bayh, Evan; Bennett, Robert F; Biggert, Judy; Bliley, Tom; Campbell, Tom; Chabot, Steve; Crane, Phillip; Crapo, Mike; Dingell, John D.; Dodd, Christopher J; Doyle, Mike; Enzi, Michael; Fowler, Tille K; Frank, Barney; Gejdenson, Sam; Grams, Rod; Isakson, Johnny; Johnson, Tim; Kanjorski, Paul E.; Latoure[...], Steven C.; Minge, David; Mink, Patsy T.; Obey, David; Oxley, Michael G.; Pitts, Joseph R; Ros-Lehtinen, Ileana; Sawyer, Thomas; Shays, Christopher; Tauzin, Billy; Torricelli, Robert; Towns, Edolphus; Voinovich, George V.; Wayne, Allard; Auditors Independence + index, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Baker, Richard H.; Bliley, Thomas J.; Gram, Phil; Greenwood, James C.; Kennedy, Edward M.; Kerry, John F.; Leach, James A.; Wyden, Ron. Banking Reform (Glass-Seagal Act; Gramm-Leach-Bliley bill), 1994 - 2000 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Bliley, Thomas J.; Burton, Dan; Dingell, John D.; Dreier, David; Fossella, Vito J.; Gramm, Phil; Livingson, Bob; Manton, Thomas; Markey, Edward J; Oxley, Michael G.; Schumer, Charles E.; Stevens, Ted; Thomas, William M; Thompson, Fred; Towns, Edolphus; Decimalization + index, 1997 - 2000 (Box 1A, Folder 1)
    - Bliley, Thomas J.; Dingell, John D.; Gore, Al; Gramm, Phil; Lasio, Rick; Markey, Edward J; Pressler, Larry; EDGAR - SEC Electronic Data Gathering Analysis and Retrieval System + index, 1993 - 1998 (Box 1A, Folder 2)
    - Burton, Dan Mutual Funds, Feb. 2000 (Box 1A, Folder 3)
    - Dingell, John D.; Markey, Edward J; Obey, David R.; Serrano, Jose E.; Towns, Edolphus; Pay Parity (H. R. 2441), Oct. 2000 (Box 1A, Folder 4)
    - D'Amato, Alphonse M; Dingell, John D.; Gramm, Phil; Markey, Edward J; Moseley-Braun, Carol; Wyden, Ron; Pay-to-Play in Municipal Bonds Market + Index, 1993 - 2000 (Box 1A, Folder 5)
    - Bliley, Thomas J.; Dingell, John D.; Fields, Jack; Greenwood, James; Hall, Ralph; Santorum, Rick; Saxton, Jim; Stevens, Ted; Payment for Order Flow/Order Handling Rules + index, 1995 - 2000 (Box 1A, Folder 6)
    - Burton, Dan; Cohen, William S.; D'Amato, Alphonse M; Dingell, John D.; Dodd, Christopher J; Dorgan, Byron L; Fields, Jack; Gillmor, Paul E.; Gore, Al; Markey, Edward J; Oxley, Michael G.;Riegle, Donald W.; Synar, Mike; Plain English, 1993 - 2000 (Box 1A, Folder 7 - 8)
    - Breeden, Richard C.; Cohen, William S.; Dingell, John D.; Division of Investment Management Plain English - correspondence of Richard C. Breeden, SEC Division of Investment Management (Box 1B, Folder 1)
    - Eshoo, Anna G.; Frank, Barney Regulation FD / Selective Disclosure, Jul. - Dec. 2000 (Box 1B, Folder 2)
    - Bliley, Thomas J.; D'Amato, Alphonse M; Dingell, John D.; Fields, Jack;Schenk, Lynn; Wyden, Ron Securities Litigation Reform, 1994 - 1998 (Box 1B, Folder 3)
    - Abraham, Spencer; Armey, Dick; Baker, Richard; Bayh, Evan; Bennett, Robert; Bilbray, Brian; Blunt, Roy; Bliley, Thomas J.; Boren, David; Bunning, Jim; Burr, Richard; Cox, Christopher; Crapo, Mike; Crowley, Joseph; Cubin, Barbara; Davis, Tom; Deal, Nathan; Deutsch, Peter; Dingell, John D.; Dooley, Cal; Dunn, Jennifer; Eshoo, Anna G.; Fossella, Vito J.; Fowler, Tillie; Gillmor, Paul E.; Gonzalez, Charles A.; Goodlatte, Bob; Gramm, Phil; Grams, Rod; Greenwood, James; Hagel, Charles; Houghton, Amo; Jeffords, James; Kind, Ron; Lieberman, Joseph; McCarthy, Carolyn; McCrerey, James; Maloney, Jim; Markey, Edward J; Moran, Jim; Myrick, Sue; Norwood, Charles W.; Oxley, Michael G.; Pickering, Charles W.; Pryce, Deborah; Roemer, Tom; Sanders, Bernard; Sandlin, Max; Santorum, Rick; Schumer, Charles; Shelby, Richard; Shimkus, John; Smith, Adam; Tauscher, Ellen; Tauzin, Billy; Torricelli, Robert; Towns, Edolphus; Udall, Mark; Upton, Fred; Waxman, Henry; Wayne, Allard; Wilson, [...]; Standards (FASB, independence), 1994 - 2000 (Box 1B, Folder 4 - 5)
      [Index in folder 1 - 41]
    - Bennett, Robert F; D'Amato, Alphonse M; Dingell, John D.; Dodd, Christopher J.; Horn, Stephen; Morella, Connie. Year 2000 Compliance, 1997 - 1999 (Box 1B, Folder 6)
    - US Senate Committee on Banking, Housing and Urban Affairs Hearing Transcript - S. 1815, Jan. 5, 1996 (Box 1B, Folder 7)
    - US House of Representatives Hearing Transcript - H. R. 3005, Jun. 18, 1996 (Box 1B, Folder 8)
    - US Senate Committee on Banking, Housing and Urban Affairs Hearing Transcript - Market Circiut Breakers, Jan. 29, 1998 (Box 1B, Folder 9)
  - Subseries II.3: SEC Copy Correspondence
    Series consists of photocopies of incoming and outgoing correspondence of Levitt as a SEC chairman. Letters are in original order - cronological (by outgoing correspondence) with threads grouped together. Thus incoming letters are usually filed immediately following the corresponding outgoing reply. In some cases incoming letters are filed both separately under their original arrival date and after the response. Correspondence, both external and internal, often includes lengthy attachments. Series is indexed by last name. (see SEC Correspondence Index) People referred to by their first name only are not indexed. Attachments, including enclosed letters to/from third parties are not indexed.
    - Congratulations on Confirmation, Jul. - Oct. 1993 (Box 1B, Folder 10)
    - Responses to Congratulations on Confirmation, Jul. - Oct. 1993 (Box 1C, Folder 1)
    - Congratulations on Re-nomination and the Longest Service, 1998 - 1999 (Box 1C, Folder 2)
    - Undated correspondence and fragments, 1993 - 2000 (Box 1C, Folder 3)
    - Personal File, 1993 - 2000 (Box 1C, Folder 4)
    - , Jul. 1993 - Dec. 1994 (Box 1C, Folder 5)
      [Aug. 1993 - Feb. 1995 formerly Box 1, folders 25 - 28]
    - , Jan. 1995 (Box 1C, Folder 6 - 7)
    - , Feb. 1995 (Box 1C, Folder 8 - 10)
    - , Mar. 1995 - Apr. 1995 (Box 2, Folder 1 - 4)
    - , May 1995 - Sep. 1995 (Box 3, Folder 1 - 5)
    - , Oct. 1995 - Jan. 1996 (Box 4, Folder 1 - 6)
    - , Feb. 1996 - Jun. 1996 (Box 5, Folder 1 - 5)
    - , Jul. 1996 - Dec. 1996 (Box 6, Folder 1 - 6)
    - , Jan. 1997 - Apr. 1997 (Box 7, Folder 1 - 5)
    - , May 1997 - Oct. 1997 (Box 8, Folder 1- 6)
    - , Nov. 1997 - Apr. 15, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 1 - 6)